A Guide to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records FA025
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1866-1998; 1; 32 Cubic Feet
  - Historical Files, 1886-1991; 3; 22.4 Cubic Feet
    - Minutes, Georgia Deeds, Corporate Documents, By Laws, 1911-1988; 13
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. - Foundation Accounting - Investment Committee Minutes, 1978-1985 (Box 48, Folder 289)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. - Foundation Accounting - Investment Committee Minutes, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 290)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. - Foundation Accounting - Investment Committee Minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 48, Folder 291)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. - Undated Papers (Box 49, Folder 292)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Trust - Miscellaneous - Trustees Minutes, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 293)
      - Culpeper Miscellaneous - Deeds to Georgia Property - Floyd County, 1911-1961 (Box 49, Folder 294)
      - Culpeper Miscellaneous - Deeds to Georgia Property - Gordon County, 1912-1932 (Box 49, Folder 295)
      - Culpeper Trust - Probate Papers, 1966-1971 (Box 49, Folder 296)
      - Historical Documents and By Laws, 1955-1960 (Box 49, Folder 297)
      - Photographs, Magazine Clippings, and Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 298)
      - Photographs, Magazine Clippings and Newspaper Clippings, 1965-1972 (Box 49, Folder 299)
    - Murray-MacDonald Foundation, Inc., 1954-1975; 14
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. - Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box 50, Folder 300)
      - Corporate Records, 1971-1975 (Box 50, Folder 301)
      - Estate of James T. Murray, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 302)
      - Murray-MacDonald Foundation, Inc., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 303)
      - James T. Murray, Personal - Carlyle Lease, 1965-1968 (Box 50, Folder 304)
      - James T. Murray, Personal - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 305)
      - James T. Murray, Personal - Will, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 306)
      - Mary Murray, 1962-1967 (Box 50, Folder 307)
        Restricted - Confidential material.
      - Mary Murray - Bank Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 308)
      - Mary Murray - Cash Receipts, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 309)
      - Mary Murray - Taxes, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 310)
      - Mary Murray - Taxes, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 311)
      - Minutes and By Laws of Murray-MacDonald Foundation, Inc., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 312)
      - Minute Book of Murray-MacDonald Foundation, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 51, Folder 313)
      - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings of Murray-MacDonald Foundation, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 314)
      - Public Inspection, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 315)
      - Financial Information, 1962-1970 (Box 51, Folder 316)
        Stock Matters, 1962-1970 Purchases, 1967 Summary Sheets, 1968
      - Tax Exemption Letter, 1955-1957 (Box 51, Folder 317)
    - New York State Tax Information, 1971-1984; 15
      - New York State - Office of the Attorney General - Charitable Foundations Division - Form NYCF-3 Securities Schedules and Associated Tax Forms - Tax Years 1971-1974 (Box 52, Folder 318)
      - New York State - Office of the Attorney General - Charitable Foundations Division - Form NYCF-3 Securities Schedules and Associated Tax Forms - Tax Years 1975-1979 (Box 52, Folder 319)
      - New York State - Office of the Attorney General - Charitable Foundations Division - Form NYCF-3 Securities Schedules and Associated Tax Forms - Tax Years 1980-1982 (Box 52, Folder 320)
      - New York State - Office of the Attorney General - Charitable Foundations Division - Form NYCF-3 Securities Schedules and Associated Tax Forms - Tax Year 1983 (Box 52, Folder 321)
      - New York State - Office of the Attorney General - Charitable Foundations Division - Form NYCF-3 Securities Schedules and Associated Tax Forms - Tax Year 1984 (Box 52, Folder 322)
    - Pleadings, 1970-1972, 1980-1981; 16
      - Application of Daphne Seybolt Culpeper - Pleadings, 1970-1971; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 323)
      - Application of Daphne Seybolt Culpeper - Pleadings, 1970-1971; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 324)
      - Culpeper vs. McNamara - Exhibits, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 325)
      - Culpeper vs. McNamara - Exhibits, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 326)
      - Culpeper Appeal from Dismissal of Petition to Remove McNamara and Johnson, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 327)
      - Culpeper Appeal of Reinstatement, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 328)
      - Culpeper Appeal of Millard Removal, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 329)
      - Culpeper Trust Removal Petitions Pleadings File, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 330)
      - In the Application of Daphne Seybolt Culpeper, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 331)
      - Millard Appeal from Dismissal of Petition to Remove McNamara and Johnson, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 332)
      - Millard Appeal of Removal, 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 333)
      - Nulman vs. Weill - Litigation, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 334)
      - Removal - Culpeper Trust Exhibits, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 335)
    - Trust Accounts and Audits, 1940-1983; 17
      - Accountings, undated (Box 55, Folder 336)
        Trustees Accounting, 1947-1948 Trust Accounting, 1949-1965
      - Charles E. Culpeper Trust - 25th Accounting, February 1, 1965-January 31, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 337)
      - 26th Accounting, February 1, 1966-January 31, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 338)
      - Accountings, undated (Box 55, Folder 339)
        27th Accounting, February 1, 1967-January 31, 1968 30th Accounting, January 31, 1969-January 31, 1970
      - 31st Accounting, February 1, 1970-January 31, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 340)
      - 32nd Accounting, February 1, 1971-January 31, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 341)
      - 33rd Accounting, February 1, 1972-January 31, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 342)
      - Accountings, undated (Box 55, Folder 343)
        34th Accounting, January 31, 1973-January 31, 1974 35th Accounting, January 31, 1974-January 31, 1975
      - Accountings, undated (Box 56, Folder 344)
        36th Accounting, January 31, 1975-January 31, 1976 37th Accounting, January 31, 1977
      - 38th Accounting, January 31-April 30, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 345)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Trust Accounting, April 30, 1977-January 31, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 346)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Trust Accounting, January 31, 1980-January 31, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 347)
      - Culpeper Audits - Financial Statements, 1966-1970 (Box 56, Folder 348)
      - Culpeper Audits - Report on Examination for the Period from February 2, 1940-January 31, 1945, undated (Box 56, Folder 349)
      - Culpeper Audits - Report on Financial Statements, 1951-1958 (Box 56, Folder 350)
      - Culpeper Audits - Report on Financial Statements, 1958-1965 (Box 56, Folder 351)
      - Culpeper Audits - Financial Statement, January 31, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 352)
      - Financial Reports and Accounting, January 1, 1945-January 31, 1946 (Box 56, Folder 353)
  - Francis J. McNamara, Jr. - Personal, 1957-1998; 4
    Series 4, Francis J. McNamara, Jr. - Personal, contains archival copies of excerpts from his appointment book as President and Chairman of the Board of the Culpeper Foundation from 1968-1999.
    - Daily Diaries, 1957-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Daily Diaries, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Daily Diaries, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Daily Diaries, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Daily Diaries, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Daily Diaries, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Daily Diaries, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Daily Diaries, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Daily Diaries, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Daily Diaries, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Daily Diaries, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Daily Diaries, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Daily Diaries, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Daily Diaries, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Daily Diaries, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Daily Diaries, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Daily Diaries, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Daily Diaries, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Daily Diaries, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Daily Diaries, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Daily Diaries, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Daily Diaries, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Daily Diaries, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Daily Diaries, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Daily Diaries, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Daily Diaries, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Daily Diaries, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Daily Diaries, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Daily Diaries, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Daily Diaries, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Daily Diaries, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Daily Diaries, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Daily Diaries, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Daily Diaries, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Daily Diaries, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Accession 2, 1875, 1878, 1916-2001 1969-2001; 2; 28 Cubic Feet
  The Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. (Culpeper Foundation) was incorporated in the State of New York on December 18, 1940, as a not-for-profit corporation devoted to charitable giving for both religious and educational purposes, with particular emphasis upon future generations. The three trustees appointed to direct the Foundation were Clarence R. Avery, President of the Chattanooga Glass Company, James T. Murray, successor to Mr. Culpeper as president and chairman of the Company's board, and Mrs. Daphne Seybolt Culpeper, a director and vice president of the company at that time. The will directed that the net income from the trust fund held with the Coca-Cola Bottling Company of New York to establish this charitable venture, was valued at $8 million. James T. Murray, also an attorney, was officer and director of the Foundation from this time until November 1968, at which time Frank J. McNamara, Jr. was elected Chairman of the Board. Under the joint leadership of Mrs. Culpeper and Board President Murray, the distribution of grant monies was made according to personal guidelines. Monies during this time period were extended to numerous institutions in less significant amounts. A detailed listing of the characteristics of the Foundation's grant program can be found in Series 2, Annual Reports, specifically in the "50th Anniversary Report, 1940-1990."
  Correspondents include: Philip M. Drake, Board Member; James W. Birkenstock, Board Member; Colin G. Campbell, Board Member; Daphne S. Culpeper (Sperl), Wife/Widow of Charles E. Culpeper, President, Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc.; Joseph F. Fahey, Jr., Board Member; Barbara Enright, Grant Administrator; William W. L. Glenn; John A. Huston; Linda E. Jacobs, Vice President for Programming; Helen D. Johnson, Vice President, Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc.; Hunter Lewis; Ronald P. Lynch; Frank J. McNamara, Jr., Chairman and President; James E. Moltz; John Morning, Board Member; Nicholas J. Nardi; Frank O'Connor, Board Member; John C. Rose, Board Member; Herman K. Scheyhing; Florence Wise, friend and correspondent to Daphne S. Culpeper (Sperl); Tadataka Yamada, Board Member.
  The second accession of the records of the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation was received in 1996 and has been processed and microfilmed. Photographs have been microfilmed and also retained in their original format (see Series 5, Photographs). Original material from Series 4, Historical Documents has not been microfilmed. Ephemera, including a commemorative sterling silver tray given to Charles E. Culpeper from the 'Managers of The Coca-Cola Bottling Company of New York' in 1937, have not been microfilmed.
  Separated Material: Separation sheets placed within the collection note material which could not be microfilmed, including a silver tray, dated 1937, and 2 corporate seals. Books removed from the collection are catalogued and available in the Archive Center's library.
  Photographs: All photographs have been microfilmed with representative institutional files. Original photographs have been retained and are stored separately from the microfilm collection. All photographs may be duplicated, pending existing copyright clearance. A complete listing of individual photographs follows.
  Books: Related monographs have not been microfilmed; the published volumes are available in the Archive Center's library. Photocopies are permitted.
  Paper formats: Manuscript materials which comprise Series 4, Historical Documents, including personal and business correspondence, pamphlets, newspaper articles, official forms, and other printed matter are available in their original format and have not been microfilmed. Photocopies are permitted.
  Accession 2 records are arranged in 6 series:
  Series A - Minutes Books and Corporate Documents
  Series 2 - Annual Reports
  Series 3 - Grants
  Series 4 - Historical Files
  Series 5 - Photographs
  Separated Materials
  The following monographs were removed from Accession 2 of the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records and placed in the Rockefeller Archive Center library. They are available for research use.
  Call Number: 025.04 ARR Author: Arrick, Ellen Title: Review of the library automation program. Imprint: Stamford: Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, 1993
  Call Number: 025.806 COM Author: Commission on Preservation and Access Title: Annual report. Imprint: Washington, D. C., 1991-1996 Added Entry: Council on Library Resources
  Call Number: Second floor library Author: Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Title: Annual report. Imprint: Stamford, 1975-2000
  Call Number: Second floor library Author: Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Title: 1940-1999 retrospective. Imprint: New York: Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 2000
  Call Number: Second floor library / 361.706 CHA Author: Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Title: 50th anniversary report, 1940-1990. Imprint: Stamford, 1991
  Call Number: 362.1 COL Title: Collaborative care: nursing case management Imprint: Chicago: American Hospital Pub. Co., 1989 Added Entry: Etheredge, Mary Lou Salome, ed.
  Call Number: 362.1 WAL Author: Walker, Gillian Title: In the midst of winter: systemic therapy with families, couples, and individuals with AIDS infection. Imprint: New York: Norton, 1991 Added Entry: Ackerman Institute AIDS and Families Project
  Call Number: 371.1 JAM Author: James, Thomas Title: Adventurous teachers, excellent schools: a report to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation. Imprint: 1991
  Call Number: 378.006 AUS Author: Austin, Ann E. Title: A good place to work: sourcebook for the academic workplace Imprint: Washington, D. C.: Council of Independent Colls., 1991 Added Entry: Rice, R. Eugene, jt. auth. -- Splete, Allen P., jt. auth.
  Call Number: 378.762 MIL Title: Millsaps: a century of vision. Imprint: Jackson, Miss.: Millsaps College, 1989 Added Entry: Cohen, Stewart Charles, ill.
  Call Number: 407 MAX Author: Maxwell, David Title: Technology and foreign language learning. Imprint: Washington, D. C.: Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, 1998
  Call Number: 610.7 PIN Author: Pinel, Philippe Title: The clinical training of doctors: an essay of 1793. Imprint: Baltimore: Johns Hopkins University Press, 1980 Notes: Insert: Weiner, Dora B. Philippe Pinel, professeur de physique medicale, d'apres des documents inedits. Added Entry: Weiner, Dora B., ed.
  Call Number: 727 WAT Author: Watson, Elizabeth L. Title: Houses for sciences: a pictorial history of Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, with Landmarks in twentieth century genetics: a series of essays by James D. Watson. Imprint: Plainview, N.Y.: Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory Pr., 1991 Notes: Inscribed by author Added Entry: Watson, James D. Landmarks in twentieth century genetics.
  Call Number: 780.7 ESP Title: Espressivo: music and life at Marlboro. Imprint: Marlboro, Vt.: Marlboro Music School and Festival, 1994 Added Entry: Snyder, J. M., ed.
  Accession 2 of the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records consists of accessions received from 1992 to 1999. An additional 2 cubic feet (approximate), which comprises Series 4 of Accession 2, was received from a private individual and accessioned in 2001.
  - Minutes Books and Corporate Documents, 1939-1999; A
    This series comprises five reels of microfilm documenting minutes of the corporation; these reels were filmed separately from Accession 2 materials.
    Series A is arranged chronologically.
    The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
    - Corporate Documents
      Appraisal
      The archival material has been reformatted and the original records are no longer available. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
      Related Materials
      Corporate documents are also found in Series 4.1, boxes 1-2, folders 1-17.
      - Corporate Structure Binder, undated (Reel 1, Frame 1)
        Tab 1 Last Will and Testament of Charles E. Culpeper, July 24, 1939
        Tab 2 Officers and Directors, June 1994
        Tab 3 Certificate of Incorporation (as amended to May 1991)
        Tab 4 By-Laws (as amended effective January 1994)
        Tab 5 Resignation of Members
        Tab 6 Certificate of Type of Not-for-Profit Corporation, January 29, 1973
        Tab 7 Opinion Letter from U.S. Treasury Department Regarding Tax Exempt Status
        Tab 8 Certificate of Authority to Transact Business in Connecticut, Certified Copy of the Application and Confirmation of Filing and Receipt Fees, January 4, 1990
        Tab 9 Certificate of Adoption of Trade name (Connecticut), November 16, 1990
        Tab 10 Historic Documents
        Tab 10a New York Charter and By-Law Documents: Certificate of Incorporation, November 18, 1955; Certificate of Change of Purposes, November 20, 1961; Certificate of Increase in Number of Directors, November 26, 1963; Certificate of Amendment, December 14, 1989; Certificate of Amendment, April 23, 1991; By-Laws as Adopted June 1978, June 13, 1978; Amendment to By-Laws, June 26, 1985; Amendment to By-Laws, June 1, 1990; By-Laws as Amended to December 1990; By-Laws as Amended to April 1993
        Tab 10b Connecticut Charter Documents: Articles of Association, December 17, 1940; Certificate of Amendment to Certificate of Incorporation, April 20, 1948; Amendment to Certificate of Incorporation, November 22, 1956; Certificate of Termination by Limitation, January 11, 1956
        Tab 10c Opinion Letter from U.S. Treasury Department (Connecticut) Regarding Tax Exempt Status, March 18, 1942
        Tab 10d Connecticut By-Law Documents: Amendment to By-Laws, May 23, 1962; Amendment to By-Laws, December 18, 1963; Amendment to By-Laws, May 27, 1964; Amendment to By-Laws, October 28, 1964; Amendment to By-Laws, November 23, 1965; Amendment to By-Laws, July 28, 1966; Amendment to By-Laws, November 5, 1970; Amendment to By-Laws, January 8, 1971; Amendment to By-Laws, June 15, 1971
      - Corporate Documents - Connecticut Corporation, undated (Reel 1, Frame 2)
        1. Original letter of exemption from Federal income tax 2. Papers in connection with application for certificates of exemption from federal income tax 3. Original agreement between Estate and Foundation re: purchase of 15,000 shares of stock; Original Note - Foundation to Estate $549,029.11 4. Connecticut amendment limiting Corporation to December 31, 1955 5. Claims against Connecticut Foundation to be sent to Mrs. Sperl
      - Corporate Documents - New York Corporation, undated (Reel 1, Frame 3)
        1. Certified copy of the Certificate of Incorporation, November 18, 1955 2. Letter of Corporation Trust Co. dated November 29, 1955 to Mr. Feigenbaum 3. Copy of Mr. Feigenbaum's letter of November 25, 1955 requesting tax exemption 4. Letter of tax exemption (original U. S. Treasury Department, December 2, 1955) 5. Photostat copy of Certificate of Change of Purposes, certified by Secretary of State, New York 6. Certificate of Increase in number of directors of Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, November 26, 1963
      - Corporate Documents - Miscellaneous, undated (Reel 1, Frame 4)
        7. Prior By-Laws excerpt (keep per Cummings & Lockwood, Ellen Stevens) 8. Original Certificate of Termination 9. Article of Association, December 17, 1940 10. Financial Statement, December 17, 1940 - January 25, 1942
    - Minute Book - Volume 1, December 18, 1940-November 2, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 1, Reel 1, Frame 5)
    - Minute Book - Volume 2, April 26, 1951-November 18, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 2, Reel 1, Frame 6)
    - Minute Book - Volume 3, December 13, 1955-August 19, 1960 (Reel 1, Frame 7, Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Minute Book - Volume 4, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 4, Reel 2, Frame 8)
    - Minute Book - Volume 5, May 23, 1962-May 27, 1964 (Reel 2, Frame 9, Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Minute Book - Volume 6, October 28, 1964-October 4, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6, Reel 2, Frame 10)
    - Minute Book - Volume 7, January 30, 1967-December 4, 1969 (Reel 2, Frame 11, Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Minute Book - Volume 8, March 16, 1970-December 14, 1971 (Reel 3, Frame 12, Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Minute Book - Volume 8a, February 2, 1962-November 28, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9, Reel 3, Frame 13)
    - Minute Book - Volume 9, March 14, 1972-December 1, 1976 (Reel 3, Frame 14, Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Minute Book - Volume 10, March 22, 1977-December 15, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11, Reel 3, Frame 15)
    - Minute Book - Volume 11, March 1, 1983-December 15, 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 16, Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Minute Book - Volume 12, March 30, 1988-December 19, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13, Reel 4, Frame 17)
    - Minute Book - Volume 13, January 3, 1991-December 14, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14, Reel 4, Frame 18)
    - Minute Book - Volume 14, March 22, 1994-December 10, 1996 (Reel 5, Frame 19, Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Minute Book - Volume 15, February 20, 1997-June 8, 1999 (Reel 5, Frame 20, Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Administration, 1942, 1977, 1980-1998; 1
    Series 1 is arranged in 9 subseries:
    Subseries 2 - Board of Trustees
    Subseries 3 - Compensation Committee
    Subseries 4 - Finance Committee
    Subseries 5 - Grants Committee
    Subseries 6 - Grants Committee and Board of Directors
    Subseries 7 - Grants Committee and Board of Trustees
    Subseries 8 - Investment Committee
    Subseries 9 - Scientific Advisory Committee
    - Board of Directors, 1977, 1988-1993; 1
      An application was considered initially by the Grants Committee of the Board of Directors. The Foundation's Board then met quarterly to consider applications recommended by the Grants Committee.
      Series 1.1 is arranged chronologically.
      - Series 1.1 - Administration - Board of Directors, 1977, 1988-1993, 1977-1993 (Reel 1, Frame 2)
      - Board of Directors Meetings - Correspondence, 1977, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 3)
      - Board of Directors Meetings - Correspondence, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 36)
      - Board of Directors Meetings - Correspondence, 1991, 1993 (Reel 1, Frame 120)
      - Board of Directors Meetings - Director of Medical Affairs, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 195)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, June 22, 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 300)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, April 4, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 303)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, June 28, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 310)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, September 14, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 317)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, September 19, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 321)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, December 13, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 334)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, April 25, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 354)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, May 21, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 372)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, June 27, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 379)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, September 18, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 401)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, October 10, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 403)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, December 19, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 421)
      - Board of Directors Meetings - Special Directors Meeting, Georgetown University, January 3, 1991 (Reel 1, Frame 432)